Marco Castiglione

marcocastiglionem@gmail.com

Summary

Software developer based in Argentina with about 9 years of professional development experience and more than 10 years as a user and developer of Blockchain solutions.

I consider myself to be a very versatile developer, meaning that I can work with different kinds of technologies as needed, learn new ones, and switch if the requirement arises.

I always take into account both the technical and business needs of a challenge, trying to do what's best for the company.

Professional experience

2023 - present - **Bloxtel.com - Staff Engineer.** Helping design and develop Bloxtel blockchain solutions.

2022 - 2023 - **Really.com - Blockchain developer.** I helped develop Really's Blockchain stack, including running private nodes, building subgraphs, rewards systems with smart contracts, complex APIs, and integrating this data with iOS mobile apps.

2023 - 2023 - Corvus Code - Lead Blockchain developer (part-time). I lead a small team of developers doing projects for different clients.

2020 - 2022 - **Ethernity.live - Full Stack Blockchain Developer.** During this time, I was involved in many projects, including:

- Lead an international team in the development of a virtual stadium project
- Developed and presented in an online conference a full-fledged secure crypto wallet
- Worked with very large and complex smart contract collections for different clients

2019 - 2020 - **Python Developer at Globant.** During this time, I deepened my knowledge of Python participating in Globant Academy during my first months, and then participated in a few projects, including one for JP Morgan.

2017 - 2019 - **Blockchain Developer at SouthX**. I worked as a Python and Solidity developer.

My achievements include co-writing an introductory book to Ethereum and

helping develop a Blockchain-based identity system. During this time, I also worked with atomic swaps.

2015 - 2017 - **SQL Developer at Banco Hipotecario**. I worked with very large Stored Procedures focused on performance, some of which could be used thousands of times each day.

Education

Globant Python Academy (2019)

University of Buenos Aires (CS, 2015-)

ProFactory - Introduction to Java (2009)

Independent programming courses (Since 2009)